<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Players</string>
    <string name="sakib">Shakib Al Hasan stands out as one of the most exceptional all-rounders in the world of cricket. Hailing from Bangladesh, Shakib has consistently showcased his prowess with both bat and ball, earning him widespread acclaim. With an impressive batting average of over 38 in Tests and nearly 35 in ODIs, along with a strike rate of around 82 in T20Is, he has proven his mettle as a reliable run-scorer across formats. Not only does he excel with the bat, but his left-arm spin bowling is equally potent, with over 200 Test wickets and more than 270 in ODIs to his name. His ability to contribute significantly in all facets of the game makes him a valuable asset for any team. </string>
    <string name="messi">Lionel Messi, the Argentine football maestro, epitomizes excellence on the pitch with his unparalleled skills and records. Messi boasts numerous accolades, including multiple Ballon dOr awards, crowning him as one of the greatest footballers of all time. He holds the record for the most goals scored in a calendar year, a testament to his goal-scoring prowess and consistency. Messis remarkable tenure at FC Barcelona saw him become the clubs all-time leading goal-scorer, captivating fans worldwide with his mesmerizing dribbles and clinical finishes. Beyond records, Messis influence transcends the sport, inspiring generations of footballers and leaving an indelible mark on the beautiful game.</string>
    <string name="ronaldo">Cristiano Ronaldo, often hailed as one of the greatest footballers of all time, has left an indelible mark on the sport with his exceptional talent and numerous records. As a prolific goal-scorer, Ronaldo holds the record for the most goals scored in the UEFA Champions League, underlining his dominance on the European stage. He has won multiple Ballon dOr awards, recognizing him as one of the top players in the world. Ronaldos versatility and athleticism have seen him excel at top clubs like Manchester United, Real Madrid, and Juventus, earning him countless domestic and international titles. Beyond records, Ronaldos dedication, work ethic, and commitment to excellence have solidified his status as an icon in the world of football.</string>
    <string name="neymar">Neymar Jr., the Brazilian football sensation, has captivated fans worldwide with his dazzling skills and records on the field. Known for his exceptional dribbling ability and flair, Neymar has earned numerous individual accolades, including being a finalist for the Ballon dOr award. He holds records for his prolific goal-scoring exploits for both club and country, showcasing his impact on the game. Neymars stint with FC Barcelona saw him form a formidable attacking trio alongside Lionel Messi and Luis Suárez, winning numerous domestic and international titles. Beyond his records, Neymars influence extends to his charismatic presence, making him one of the most iconic figures in modern football.</string>
    <string name="rock">Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson, a towering figure in both wrestling and entertainment, has left an indelible mark on pop culture. During his illustrious wrestling career, The Rock became a multiple-time WWE Champion and headlined several iconic matches, cementing his legacy as one of the greatest performers in WWE history. Transitioning to Hollywood, The Rock has starred in numerous blockbuster films, consistently proving his box office appeal and earning critical acclaim. Beyond his entertainment endeavors, The Rock holds records for his philanthropic efforts, often using his platform to inspire and uplift others. With his charisma, talent, and dedication, The Rock continues to be a beloved figure, leaving a lasting impact on audiences worldwide.</string>
    <string name="tamim">Tamim Iqbal, a prominent cricketer from Bangladesh, has left an indelible mark on the international cricketing scene. Known for his aggressive batting style at the top of the order, Tamim has been a key figure in Bangladeshs cricketing journey. With over 4000 runs in Test matches at an average of around 39, and more than 7000 runs in ODIs with an average of approximately 36, he has been a consistent run-scorer for his team. His ability to adapt to different conditions and oppositions has earned him respect worldwide. Tamims explosive batting at the start of an innings often sets the tone for Bangladeshs innings. Tamim Iqbals impressive statistics and impactful performances make him a true cricketing icon for Bangladesh.</string>
</resources>